No matter how bad your luck is,
if you are good then the bill will always be good with you.
Look at this thing, the gas,
look, I did not get it, it means it is completely broken
and some part inside
is broken and if you keep thinking about this then
your work will never be done, always remember this thing,
so like, this is a service center,
washing is done inside here and as
much as it looked bad for a long time, there is a
look of shame from the TVS people, the business is as bad as it was in the morning,
now I am leaving the
TVS showroom, I had to get the
insurance claim done for my TVS Entorq
and I don't know friend, what are the TVS people doing,
what are they doing, they are
giving date after date, if not then they have changed the date thrice, my
mind is completely confused, I am
not getting the date, yesterday I called them and told them
what are you people doing, I am coming today
and you people should take it from the like
because whatever was in my estimate has
come long ago, there has been only one like,
today the video is still not seeing the response, so
this thing is less  I
felt very bad that the response from the TVS lady on the date menu was
so bad and I am also going to the
showroom and I just like I
adjusted something in my helmet, what is actually happening with the mount,
I am
shooting block and I am throwing the helmet on, so
I am getting very heavy in the helmet
and I am getting so much pain in the back side and the
phone is falling down again and again, so it did
not fit me properly, I have
adjusted a lot in the helmet, so let's see
if I get the shot now and now let's go
in the scooter, gas and we will talk about the rest of these things on the
way, so let's go
[Music] I
hope you guys are feeling
fine, I have
not yet seen for myself how I am getting the view,
how not, I have
set it with a little difficulty, I have worn the helmet,
I have given a cloth around it so that it becomes a
little tight,
I am thinking of looking for a new helmet, but I do
n't have any plans right now, the only plan is that it is a
vehicle, everything should be fine in it.
Last time I went to the showroom,
I had to look at the map as well, so I had to
block it in between and I wo
n't be able to leave it to you guys directly. It takes a little bit of
time to see it. The people who look around
think what does a girl mean,
who understands what, and I just want to keep my job. If I
think about someone else, I will never get
my job. Always remember this thing.
Right now, it's okay, it's not that sunny, it's
6:30 kilometers from my side, I will have to
think about it, I haven't fueled up,
because if I give it for service, then who
knows, I have to take it out,
but the brakes are not that good that I will kill me
with breakfast. I will have to get the brakes changed too,
friend, I will have to tell you what all needs to be
changed, so it
could be that there's
very little sunlight here. Actually,
I like shooting a lot.
I like about like action cameras, so
for now, until you do
n't have subscribers, I wo
n't even think about like action because
all those things, whenever you guys  It shoots,
growth is happening and it continues to be powerful,
so what happens in that thing, when you
invest, then it also feels like
you have invested something, so take it, I do
n't like to wait at all,
if you people do not know like how
I met with the accident of my scooter and how it did
not happen, then you will get that detailed video
in three sections and in the second video, I
gave a small lecture
about insurance, how to play in your bike,
so stopping, I gave a small lecture of
5 minutes, so you can watch that too, I will give that
also in the height button in life, here
some liking and uploading is happening, so this
thing for the difference is gas like, whatever the vehicles that are available
in the 150 125 section, whatever the vehicles that are
available, whatever the
vehicles that are available, whatever the scooters that are
available, the most produced
snow van is 60 which is the top speed which is
160 upon the first actually you are Android, I
can say clearly because its mileage is
not good because someone please tell me brother what is the mileage of the difference
because I do not know the video  If you
get a mileage of 32 or 35, then it will be around 32 or 35
and only some great person
can say that if they get 40, then it is a
big thing for them because all the
Android scooters that have been launched are just for now, for now, these are four
models, the rest of the scooters that are coming
now, in fact, many
like, so many digital, so many functions
etc. have come, so brother, I am getting
amazed to see them because now such a thing has
come, if you are
standing in traffic and your time in traffic is
more than 20 to 30 seconds,
then your automatic
engine will turn off and it is
not like that here, we have to take some measures,
like if there is traffic, then
close the door and turn on the boom, but still it is fine according to you, the
vehicles that are coming now, when I
bought it from yellow in 2020, then at that time it was
very oily, very much
jyada.com and the most special thing about this
scooter is its exhaust sound, you will
not even feel that brother, this  This exhaust is of a
scooter, you have definitely liked it because
this is of the S 125 etc.
type of section, so right
now I talk too much, so
you guys enjoy a little, I will
close this blog for now, but till date I do
n't have a proper idea how to
come, I am just getting approximate as far as I know,
after that
I will stop liking,
like in Kolkata, hey friend, who likes so much,
their attitude is of next level,
and if you ask me anything now, like brother, some
help and all but no response, nothing, those
people do not want to do it, brother, I do
not want to become like this, if you people make me do anything, I will do it
100%, if
I have any person, anyone, I will
show my support by wearing eggs, which you find strange,
and you are telling that thing to someone, then
you also get to learn something, the
intelligence, the knowledge, from you.  I cannot buy anything,
you can share it, in fact your
knowledge can increase. I have given you the
scooter, it is
said here what all has been
changed and what all is not there, I would have
shown you what problems there were in the scooter, that is why
I have come near the service center,
so next I will show you the service center,
here washing is done
inside and all the
bike services are done and here is the
building and this is my scooter and tok
silver color, here the 125 side is completely
broken and some of the inside parts are broken
and
something here is also broken, this
side of the inside will be changed and I will tell you its price
when I get the scooter completely
proper in hand and the front brake was also having a
complete issue, so here I said that there is some
cash problem, so I will
see about it later and right now I have said that please repair my rear
brake, so
brother, I have told about the rear
brake and all the parts that were there, see this thing,
gas, see this is not there.  I have
n't got it out
oh brother
and that was the only problem I had and right now it's quite
crowded here this
service center has become here and all the other
car owners who live there are all
lined up here for service you
can see I mean it's good here no matter how
bad your luck is
if you are good then you will always get a
good bill so a similar situation happened with me
I had gone to the showroom but to
come back from there I had to take a lot of rounds
because I had to change the bus then
two and then I had to come home so it was already
afternoon I rarely travel I was
in the showroom I met a random guy and just on the
topic I started talking about
what's the problem with your scooter because he had also
bought a scooter and his score was the van man in the team so
his scooter too like
TVS and 125 something of this race which was just
now
[Sangeet] so
I just friend I have
exchanged a lot of numbers and that too at the same cost
you moto guys so I also  If you want to
make me a model then I am
fine, you can go and you can also join the
group because we are making groups
for trips, some small or
long trips, then we think that we
cannot confirm anything right now what to do or
not, from there the like scene happened, then that guy
dropped me halfway
and Sachi, those people were very good hearted
because in today's time it is very difficult
that even if you have everything available, you go very far
behind and
instead of help they say let's
see and all, so I am
telling you honestly, you people should stay away from all those people
because then you will definitely have some motive, so
that sweet boy was very nice
and like half the milk to me is
Rajasthani
[music]
so this thing, this is a help, someone else does it
and now if you ever do it to someone else, that is
why I am getting happiness from this, so
you will also
get happiness in that time, help, whatever it is, I have
given the scooter to my showroom and they have
said that they will call me in two or three days.
M will have to go to buy a scooter,
so it's okay, gas, and what should I say,
if I become a scooterist, then I will
make a proper chart of what all I spent in life, TVS and what all I did
not,
and in future, if you also get a scooter, then
you will get an example article that
yes, this part can be so powerful, then I will
make a video of DD for that
in the next blog, when I will have enough,
I have a scooter in my hand, so for
now, I am turning off the gauge,
blocked because my hand is already broken, and I fell
asleep while coming home,
if you have come to the channel, you have stopped, you have come this far, then
please like and subscribe, if you like it, I will
motivate you, I will do more video songs in future,
you guys also keep giving me some love, I will
also keep laughing with love, so see you
brother